<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resources on /home/talayhan</title>
    <link>/tags/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resources on /home/talayhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 11:06:40 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Free Learning Resources</title>
      <link>/posts/free-learning-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 11:06:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/free-learning-resources/</guid>
      <description>Many publishers are temporarily providing free access to eBooks/slides/videos and other eContent during the COVID-19 crisis. I&amp;rsquo;ve arranged some of them I like. Please find below.
 Security, Pentesing, InfoSec - Web Link Exploit Development - Web Link Total OSCP Guide - Web Link Creating a Rootkit to Learn C - Web Link The TCP/IP Guide - Web Link Advanced SQL and database books and resources - Web Link Syncfusion - software development, data visualization, and data science - Web Link Mastering Embedded Linux - Blog Series - Web Link Course materials for Modern Binary Exploitation by RPISEC - Web Link OSCP Human Guide - Web Link Learn Regex by Examples - Web Link Mastering GNU Awk - Web Link Javascript Info - Web Link Malware Analysis course at University of Cincinnati, Jan 2020-Apr 2020 - Web Link Teach Yourself Computer Science - Web Link Deep Dive Into Modern Web Development - Web Link Malware Analysis Traning - Web Link Hundreds of freely accessible courses from METU - Web Link  Computer Engineering - Web Link  C Homework Collection - Very Best - Web Link Data Structure - Very Best - Web Link     Awesome Reverse Engineering - Web Link Algorithm 101 from MIT - Web Link - Exams and Solutions C/C++ Books - Web Link  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
